chillibreeze.com 2017-07-07

# Privacy Policy

## Important Information

This privacy policy sets out how Chillibreeze.com uses and protects any information that you give Chillibreeze when you use this website. Chillibreeze is committed to ensuring that your privacy is always safeguarded. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Chillibreeze may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes.

### What we collect

We may collect the following information:

  1. Name 
  2. Contact information including email address
  3. Demographic information such as postcode, street address and country
  4. Other information relevant to customer surveys and/or offers

### What we do with the information we gather

We require this information to understand your needs and provide you with the best in presentation aids, and in particular for the following reasons:

  1. Internal record keeping
  2. We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  3. We may periodically send promotional emails about new products, special offers or other information which we think you may find interesting using the email address which you have provided.
  4. We may use the information to customize the website according to your interests.

### Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. In order to prevent unauthorized access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.

### How we use cookies

A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. Once you agree, the file is added and the cookie helps analyze web traffic or lets you know when you visit a particular site. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyze data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system.

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website.

### Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question.

### How to contact Chillibreeze

**Online form**  \- The fastest way to contact Chillibreeze is by completing our online form. We will get back to you within one working day.  
**By Post**  \- If you wish to send us a letter, please write to  
Customer Services  
Chillibreeze Solutions Pvt. Ltd.  
Software Technology Park of India,  
Lawmali, Shillong, Meghalaya - 793001  
India
